

 \times

cedricharris118@gmail.com



+86 591 908 8300



Beijing, China



live:.cid.74919c939a539319



github.com/paizongnan

SKILLS

swift

OBJECTIVE-C

JAVA

KOTLIN

React.js

Node.js

Express.js

Angular/CLI

PYTHON

PHP

Vue.is

Tailwind

LANGUAGES

ENGIISH

Full Professional Proficiency

CHINESE

Full Professional Proficiency

ESPAÑOL

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

snowboarding

science fiction novels

Rock climbing

Football

Meng Rang

iOS/Android/Web Engineer

Do you need a dedicated developer who can help to create your site? I'm a full stack developer with 10+ years experience. My intention is to form a trusting working relationship by demonstrating total dedication and commitment to each individual project, no matter the size or the difficulty of the task at hand. I believe communication is key to any successful project.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Stepping Stone Advertising, New York

10/2017 - 01/2020 Achievements/Tasks

- Responsible for several projects for clients including multiple Swift iOS applications, React Native (iOS & Android) applications, Android TV applications and backend systems for each project.
- As defacto team lead within the organization I was responsible for each client project as it came in and was passed through the development pipeline, working with every part of the application development lifecycle and working to meet client expectations while balancing time and effort.

SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPERStepping Stone Advertising, New York

02/2020 - 07/2022

Achievements/Tasks

- Full Stack Development with NodeJS, ExpressJS and React Native (iOS & Android).
- Setup and maintained CI/CD pipelines to multiple environments including backend, web and mobile app beta and production distributions.
- Mentored and trained multiple junior developers on staff and lead the development team from the start of the project up to over 5000 users and 15 team members.

LEAD BACKEND DEVELOPERExperion, New York

08/2022 - Present New York

Achievements/Tasks

- NodeJS, TypeScript. Lead DevOps with AWS including Elastic Beanstalk, Lambda, S3 and more.
- AI/ML service identification, development and integration.
- Database development with MongoDB. Working with large video data while managing infrastructure costs with rapid scaling in mind.
- Frontend iOS (Swift) API integration. Managing CI/CD pipelines, Github repositories, providing Github training and reviewing contributions.
- Managing infrastructure security and compliance for employee and user data.
- Delegate tasks to the 7 members of the developer team and provide counsel on all aspects of the project.

EDUCATION

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE TSINGHUA UNIVERSITY

02/2012 - 08/2016

MASTER OF MATHEMATICS University of Cambridge

01/2017 - 02/2020

Cambridge , United Kingdom

Beijing ,China

New York

New York